Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Well. if this is it.
old boy.
I hope you don't mind
if I go out
speaking the King's.
By all means.
Captain.
There's a special rung in hell
reserved for people who waste
good Scotch.
Seeing as I may be rapping
on the door momentarily.
I must say.
damn good stuff. sir.
Now. about this pickle
we find ourselves in.
lt would appear there's only
one thing left for you to do.
And what would that be?
Stiglitz.
Say auf Wiedersehen
to your Nazi balls.
You outside.
Who are you?
British? American?
What?
ALDO: We're American.
What are you?
I'm a German. you idiot.
ALDO: Speak English
pretty good for a German.
I agree.
So let's talk.
Okay. talk.
I'm a father.
My baby was born today.
ln Frankfurt.
Five hours ago.
His name is Max.
We were in here
drinking. celebrating.
They're the ones that came in
shooting and killing.
It's not my fault!
Okay!
lt wasn't your fault.
What's your name.
soldier?
Wilhelm.
Now. is there anybody alive
on our side?
No.
I'm alive!
ALDO: Who's that?
Is the girl
on your side?
Which girl?
Who do you think?
Von Hammersmark.
Yeah. she's ours.
Is she okay?
Wilhelm!
She's been shot.
But she's alive.
ALDO: Okay. Wilhelm.
What do you say
we make us a deal?
What's your name?
Aldo.
Okay. Wilhelm.
here's my deal.
You let me and one of my men
come down there
and take the girl away.
No guns. No guns me.
no guns you.
And we take the girl
and leave.
It's that simple. Willi.
You go your way.
we go ours.
And little Max gets
to grow up playing
catch with his daddy.
So what do you say. Willi?
We got us a deal?
Aldo.
I'm here. Willi.
I want to trust you.
But...
But how can l?
What choice you got.
son?
Okay. okay.
Aldo.
I'm going to trust you.
Come down.
Hey. Willi.
what's with the machine gun?
l thought we had us a deal?
We still have a deal.
Now. get the girl and go.
Not so fast.
We only got a deal.
we trust each other.
And a Mexican standoff
ain't trust.
You need guns on me
for it to be
a Mexican standoff.
You got guns on us.
You decide to shoot.
we're dead.
Up top. they got grenades.
They drop them down here.
you're dead.
That's a Mexican standoff.
and that was not the deal.
No trust.
no deal.
All right. Aldo.
Fine.
Just take that
fucking traitor. and
get her out of my sight.
Not so goddamn fast. doc.
Tell him to go
play with his dogs.
Before we yank that slug
out you. you need to answer
a few questions.
Few questions
about what?
About I got three men
dead back there.
Why don't you try telling us
what the fuck happened?
The British officer
blew his German act and
the Gestapo major saw it.
Before we get into
who shot John.
why'd you invite my men
to a rendezvous in a basement
with a bunch of Nazis?
I can see
since you didn't see
what happened inside.
that the Nazis being there
must look odd.
Yeah. we got a word
for that kind of odd
in English.
It's called suspicious.
Everybody needs
to calm down.
You're letting
your imagination get
the better of you.
You met the sergeant
yourself. Willi.
You remember him.
don't you?
Yeah. I remember him.
His wife had
a baby tonight.
He had just become a...
He had just become
a father!
His commanding officer
gave him and his mates
the night off to celebrate.
The Germans being there
was either a trap set by me
or a tragic coincidence.
It couldn't be both.
How'd the shooting start?
The Englishman
gave himself away.
How'd he do that?
He ordered three glasses.
We order three glasses.
That's the German three.
The other looks odd.
Germans would
and did notice it.
Okay. let's pretend
there were no Germans
and everything went exactly
the way it was supposed to.
What was the next step?
Tuxedos.
To get them into the premiere
wearing military uniforms
with all the military there
would've been suicide.
But going as members
of the German film industry.
they wear tuxedos
and fit in with
everybody else.
I arranged for the tailor
to fit three tuxedos tonight.
How'd you intend to get them
in that premiere?
Hand me my purse.
Lieutenant Hicox
was going as my escort.
The other two were going
as a German cameraman
and his assistant.
You still get us
in that premiere?
You speak German
better than
your friends? No.
Have I been shot? Yes!
I don't see me tripping
the light fantastique up
a red carpet anytime soon.
Least of all.
by tomorrow night.
However. there's something
you don't know.
There've been
two recent developments
regarding Operation Kino.
One. the venue has been
changed from The Ritz
to a much smaller venue.
Enormous change
at the last minute?
That's not very Germatic.
Why the hell is Goebbels
doing stuff so damn peculiar?
It probably has
something to do with
the second development.
Which is?
Der Fuhrer is attending
the premiere.
Fuck a duck!
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking getting
a whack at planting
old Uncle Adolf
makes this horse
a different color.
What is that
supposed to mean?
lt means you getting us
in that premiere.
I'm probably going
to end up losing this leg.
Bye-bye. acting career.
Fun while it lasted.
How do you expect me
to walk the red carpet?
Doggy doc's going
to dig that slug
out your gam.
He's going to wrap it up
in a cast.
and you got a good
how-l-broke-my-leg-
mountain-climbing story.
That's German. ain't it?
You all like climbing
mountains. don't you?
I don't. I like smoking.
drinking and ordering
in restaurants.
But I see your point.
We fill you up
with morphine till it's
coming out your ears
and just limp
your little ass up
that reuge carpet.
I know this is
a silly question
before I ask it.
but can you Americans
speak any other language
than English?
We both speak
a little Italian..
With an atrocious accent.
no doubt.
But that doesn't exactly
kill us in the crib.
Germans don't have
a good ear for Italian..
So you mumble Italian.
and brazen through it.
Is that the plan?
That's about it.
That sounds good.
It sounds like shit.
What else are we going
to do? Go home?
No. that sounds good.
If you don't blow it.
with that. I can get
you in the building.
Who does what?
Well.
I speak the most Italian..
so I'll be your escort.
Donowitz speaks second most.
so he'll be
your Italian cameraman.
Omar. third most.
He'll be Donny's assistant.
I don't speak Italian..
Like I said. third best.
Just keep your
fucking mouth shut.
In fact.
why don't you start
practicing right now?
Yes.
Gorlomi?
Gorlomi.
Antonio Margheriti.
Margheriti.
HANS: Margheriti.
Dominick Decocco.
What's that
American expression?
"If the shoe fits.
you must wear it."
ALDO: Fucking shithead.
Faggot fuck. Fuck you!
Bunch of shithead fuck.
Fuck you. too!
Goddamn Nazi farts.
sons of bitches!
Get your hands off me.
You fucking
bratwurst-smelling...
Goddamn you! Get off!
Hmm.
You Jerry-banging.
Limburg-smelling...
As Stanley said
to Livingstone.
Lieutenant Aldo Raine.
I presume?
Hans Landa.
You've had
a nice long run. Aldo.
Alas. you're now
in the hands of the SS.
My hands to be exact.
And they've been waiting
a long time to touch you.
Caught you flinching.
ALDO: Touch me again.
Kraut-burger.
Utivich?
Is that you.
Lieutenant?
Yeah.
Do you know
what happened to Donny?
Omar?
The woman?
No. I do not.
Tell me. Aldo.
if I were sitting
where you're sitting.
would you
show me mercy?
Nope.
What is that
English expression
about shoes and feet?
"Looks like the shoe is
on the other foot." Yeah.
I was just thinking that.
So you're Aldo the Apache.
So you're The Jew Hunter.
I'm a detective.
A damn good detective.
Finding people
is my specialty.
so naturally.
I worked for the Nazis
finding people.
And. yes.
some of them were Jews.
But Jew Hunter?
Just a name that stuck.
Well. you do
have to admit.
it is catchy.
Do you control the nicknames
your enemies bestow on you?
Aldo the Apache
and the Little Man?
What do you mean
the Little Man?
Germans' nickname for you.
The Germans' nickname for me
is the Little Man?
And as if to make my point.
I'm a little surprised how
tall you were in real life.
I mean.
you're a little fellow. but
not circus-midget little.
as your reputation
would suggest.
Where's my men?
Where's
Bridget von Hammersmark?
Well. let's just say.
she got what she deserved.
And when you purchase
friends like Bridget
von Hammersmark.
you get what you pay for.
Now as far as your paesanos.
Sergeant Donowitz
and Private Omar...
How you know our names?
Lieutenant Aldo.
if you don't think
I wouldn't interrogate
every single one of your
swastika-marked survivors.
we simply aren't
operating on the level of
mutual respect I assumed.
No. I guess not.
Well. back to
the whereabouts of your
two Italian. saboteurs.
As of this moment.
both Omar and Donowitz
should be sitting in the
very seats we left them in.
Double-zero 23
and double-zero 24.
if my memory serves.
Explosives
still around their ankles.
still ready to explode.
And your mission.
some would call
a terrorist plot.
as of this moment.
is still a go.
That's a pretty
exciting story.
What's next? Eliza on lce?
However.
all I have to do is pick up
this phone right here.
inform the cinema.
and your plan is kaput.
If they're still here.
and if they're still alive.
and that's one big if.
there ain't no way
you're going
to take them boys
without setting off
them bombs.
I have no doubt.
And. yes.
some Germans will die.
Yes. it will ruin the evening.
And. yes. Goebbels will be
very. very. very mad at you
for what you've done
to his big night.
But you won't get Hitler.
you won't get Goebbels.
you won't get Goring.
and you won't get Bormann.
And you need all four
to end the war.
But if I don't pick up
this phone right here.
you may very well
get all four.
And if you get all four.
you end the war
tonight.
So. gentlemen.
let's discuss the prospect
of ending the war tonight.
So. the way I see it.
since Hitler's death
or possible rescue rests
solely on my reaction.
if I do nothing.
it's as if
I'm causing his death
even more than yourselves.
Wouldn't you agree?
I guess so.
How about you.
Utivich?
I guess so. too.
Gentlemen.
l have no intention
of killing Hitler and killing
Goebbels and killing Goring
and killing Bormann.
not to mention winning
the war single-handedly
for the Allies.
only later
to find myself standing
before a Jewish tribunal.
If you want to win
the war tonight.
we have to make a deal.
What kind of deal?
The kind you wouldn't
have the authority to make.
However. I'm sure
this mission of yours has
a commanding officer.
A general.
I'm betting for...
OSS would be my guess.
That's a bingo!
Is that the way you say it?
"That's a bingo."
You just say. "Bingo."
Bingo! How fun.
But I digress.
Where were we?
Yeah! Make a deal.
Over there is a very capable
two-way radio
and sitting behind it
is a more than capable
radio operator named Hermann.
Get me someone
on the other end
of that radio
with the power of the pen
to authorize my.
let's call it.
the terms of my
conditional surrender.
If that tastes better
going down.
You know.
where I'm from...
Yeah?
Where is that exactly?
Maynardville.
Tennessee.
I've done my share
of bootlegging.
Up there. if you engage
in what the federal government
calIs illegal activity.
but what we call just a man
trying to make a living
for his family
selling moonshine liquor.
it behooves oneself
to keep his wits.
Long story short.
we hear a story
too good to be true.
it ain't.
Sitting in your chair.
l would probably
say the same thing.
and 999. 999 times
out of a million.
you would be correct.
But in the pages of history.
every once in a while.
fate reaches out
and extends its hand.
What shall
the history books read?
MAN: I implore you.
We must destroy that tower.
Sarge. that tower...
MAN: The tower stands!
Psst! Psst!
HANS: So when
the military history
of this night is written.
it will be recorded
that I was part
of Operation Kino
from the very beginning
as a double agent.
Anything I've done
in my guise
as an SS Colonel
was sanctioned by the OSS
as a necessary evil
to establish my cover
with the Germans.
And it was my placement
of Lieutenant Raine's
dynamite
in Hitler and Goebbels'
opera box that
assured their demise.
By the way.
that last part
is actually true.
I want my full
military pension and benefits
under my proper rank.
I want to receive
the Congressional
Medal of Honor
for my invaluable assistance
in the toppling
of the Third Reich.
In fact.
I want all the members
of Operation Kino
to receive the
Congressional Medal of Honor.
Full citizenship for myself.
Well. that goes
without saying.
And I would like
the United States of America
to purchase property for me
on Nantucket lsland
as a reward for all
the countless lives
I've saved
by bringing the tyranny
of the National
Socialist Party
to a swifter-than-imagined
end. Do you have
all that. sir?
I look forward to seeing you
face to face as well. sir.
Lieutenant Raine?
Right here.
Yes. sir.
GENERAL: Colonel Landa will
put you and Private Utivich
in a truck as prisoners.
Then he and his radio operator
will get in the truck
and drive to our lines.
Upon crossing our lines.
Colonel Landa and his man
will surrender to you.
You will then take over
driving of the truck
and bring them straight
to me for debriefing.
Is that clear. Lieutenant?
Yes. sir.
Over and out.
When I kill that guy.
you got 30 feet
to get to that guard.
Can you do it?
I have to.
Champagne?
Who wants to send
a message to Germany?
I have a message
for Germany.
That you are
all going to die.
And I want you to look deep
into the face of the Jew
who's going to do it!
Marcel. burn it down.
Oui. Shosanna.
My name
is Shosanna Dreyfus.
and this is the face
of Jewish vengeance.
HANS: Hermann.
uncuff them.
I'm officially surrendering
myself over to you.
Lieutenant Raine.
We're your prisoners.
How about my knife?
Thank you very much.
Colonel.
Utivich. cuff
the Colonel's hands
behind his back.
Is that really
necessary?
I'm a slave
to appearances.
Scalp Hermann.
Are you mad?
What have you done?
I made a deal
with your general
for that man's life!
Yeah. they made that deal.
But they don't give a fuck
about him. They need you.
You'll be shot for this!
Nah. I don't think so.
More like chewed out.
I've been chewed out before.
You know. Utivich and myself
heard that deal you made
with the brass.
End the war tonight?
I'd make that deal.
How about you. Utivich?
You make that deal?
I'd make that deal.
I don't blame you.
Damn good deal.
And that pretty little nest
you feathered for yourself.
Well. if you're
willing to barbecue
the whole High Command.
l suppose that's worth
certain considerations.
But I do have
one question.
When you get
to your little place
on Nantucket lsland.
l imagine you are going to
take off that handsome-looking
SS uniform of yours.
Ain't you?
That's what I thought.
Now. that I can't abide.
How about you. Utivich.
can you abide it?
Not one damn bit. sir.
I mean.
if I had my way.
you'd wear that
goddamn uniform for the rest
of your pecker-sucking life.
But I'm aware
that ain't practical.
I mean. at some point.
you're going to have
to take it off.
So.
I'm going to give you
a little something
you can't take off.
You know something.
Utivich?
I think this just might be
my masterpiece.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm